(sniffles)
You're right.
(Bernadette:)Now where did we land
on my bathroom?
(door opening)
(Sheldon:)Hey.
(Sheldon:)Hello.
(Leonard:)How come you're up so late?
(Sheldon:)I posted the last episode
(Sheldon:)of Fun with Flags hours ago,
(Sheldon:)and not a single person
cared enough to comment.
(Sheldon:)All that effort for nothing.
(Leonard:)Mm. I know how you feel.
(Leonard:)I spent the day throwing out
a man's entire career,
(Leonard:)and all that's left is
an old bottle of champagne
(Leonard:)and a naked lady pen
that Raj took
(Leonard:)when he thought
no one was looking.
(Sheldon:)It's not the same thing.
(Sheldon:)I don't think you know
how I feel at all.
(Leonard:)Sad?
(Sheldon:)Hmm. You do get me.
(computer chimes)
(Sheldon:)Someone left a comment.
(Leonard:)Yeah. What did they say?
"Too bad your show is done.
I kind of liked it."
(Sheldon:)Leonard, did you hear that?